Andrew Eisenberg collection of East African commercial sound recordings AD.MC.035
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
- Series III: Audiocassettes
  - Maulidi Juma 22: Maulidi Juma, AD_MC_035_ref1066; 1 Cassettes
  - Maulidi Juma 23: Maulidi Juma, AD_MC_035_ref1067; 1 Cassettes
  - Maulidi Juma 24: Maulidi Juma, AD_MC_035_ref1068; 1 Cassettes
  - Maulidi Juma 6: Maulidi Juma, AD_MC_035_ref1069; 1 Cassettes
  - Metro (B) Modern Taarab: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1070; 1 Cassettes
  - Mkukimoyoni: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1071; 1 Cassettes
  - Moh'd Shali Vol - 9: Moh'd Shali, AD_MC_035_ref1072; 1 Cassettes
  - Moh'd Yusuf Tenge No. 17: Moh'd Yusuf Tenge, 2004; AD_MC_035_ref1073; 1 Cassettes
  - Moh'd Lali 2: [Unknown], AD_MC_035_ref1074; 1 Cassettes
  - Mohamed Shali 10: Mohamed Shali, AD_MC_035_ref1075; 1 Cassettes
  - Mombasa Kisiwani: Simba Wanyika, Arusha Jazz, AD_MC_035_ref1076; 1 Cassettes
  - Mukrim Songs: Mukrim, 2000; AD_MC_035_ref1077; 1 Cassettes
  - Mwanahela & Party: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1078; 1 Cassettes
  - Mwanzele 7: Ngambo Wa Hare, AD_MC_035_ref1080; 1 Cassettes
  - Mwenye Wivuajinyonge: Zanzibar Stars Modern Taarab: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1081; 1 Cassettes
  - New Bhalo No. 2: Bhalo & Party, AD_MC_035_ref1083; 1 Cassettes
  - New Bhalo No. 4: Bhalo & Party, AD_MC_035_ref1084; 1 Cassettes
  - New Bhalo No. 5: Bhalo & Party, AD_MC_035_ref1085; 1 Cassettes
  - New Bhalo No. 11: Bhalo & Party, AD_MC_035_ref1086; 1 Cassettes
  - New Bhalo No. 13: Bhalo & Party, AD_MC_035_ref1087; 1 Cassettes
  - New Bhalo No. 16: Bhalo & Party, AD_MC_035_ref1088; 1 Cassettes
  - New Bhalo No. 18: Bhalo & Party, AD_MC_035_ref1089; 1 Cassettes
  - New Bhalo No. 19: Bhalo & Party, AD_MC_035_ref1090; 1 Cassettes
  - New Bhalo No. 20: Bhalo & Party, AD_MC_035_ref1091; 1 Cassettes
  - New-Star 8: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1092; 1 Cassettes
  - Ni Hukumu Ya Mahaba: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1093; 1 Cassettes
  - Noour Ul Oyoon Zanzibar C-90: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1094; 1 Cassettes
  - Nyerere Konde: Nyerere Konde, AD_MC_035_ref1095; 1 Cassettes
  - Old Bhalo No. 1: Bhalo & Party, AD_MC_035_ref1096; 1 Cassettes
  - Old Bhalo No. 6: [Unknown], AD_MC_035_ref1097; 1 Cassettes
  - Qaswida: Mohamed Kadara, AD_MC_035_ref1098; 1 Cassettes
  - Qaswida 1: Markaz Swalihina, AD_MC_035_ref1099; 1 Cassettes
  - Qaswida 2: Markaz Swalihina, AD_MC_035_ref1100; 1 Cassettes
  - Ripoti Kamili: Wagosi wa kaya, AD_MC_035_ref1101; 1 Cassettes
  - Samai Abdulrahim: Samai Abdulrahim, AD_MC_035_ref1102; 1 Cassettes
  - Sauti Ya Dhahabu: TID/Khalid Mohamed, 2002; AD_MC_035_ref1103; 1 Cassettes
  - Segere: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1104; 1 Cassettes
  - Kali Za Taarab: Shakila, AD_MC_035_ref1105; 1 Cassettes
  - Si Basi Tu: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1106; 1 Cassettes
  - Silver Star No.1: Tetemeko la Jiji: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1107; 1 Cassettes
  - SilverStar No. 2: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1108; 1 Cassettes
  - Silverstars Taarab: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1109; 1 Cassettes
  - Silverstars Taarab: Mtoto Sandra: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1110; 1 Cassettes
  - Simba Wanyika in Europe: Simba Wanyika, AD_MC_035_ref1111; 1 Cassettes
  - Simba Wanyika, Arusha Jazz: Simba Wanyika, Arusha Jazz, AD_MC_035_ref1112; 1 Cassettes
  - Slim Ali 432: Slim Ali, AD_MC_035_ref1113; 1 Cassettes
  - Slim Ali Vol. 2: [Unknown], AD_MC_035_ref1114; 1 Cassettes
  - Sumu Pendo Lako Sumu: Yusuf Mohamed (Tenge), AD_MC_035_ref1115; 1 Cassettes
  - Taarab Vol - 29: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1116; 1 Cassettes
  - Taarab Vol One Zilipendwa: Bakari Abeid, AD_MC_035_ref1117; 1 Cassettes
  - Talented Melody Modern Taarab: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1118; 1 Cassettes
  - Talented Melody Modern Taarab: Siti Mbili Kwa Idadi: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1118.5; 1 Cassettes
  - Tanzania One Theatre: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1119; 1 Cassettes
  - Tega Sikio: Caz T, AD_MC_035_ref1120; 1 Cassettes
  - The Best of African Songs: Safari Sound Band, AD_MC_035_ref1121; 1 Cassettes
  - The Best Of Rusha Roho: [Compilation], 2002; AD_MC_035_ref1122; 1 Cassettes
  - The Best of Rusha Roho 2002: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1123; 1 Cassettes
  - The Golden Voice Of Juma Bhalo JB. Volume 27: Juma Bhalo, AD_MC_035_ref1124; 1 Cassettes
  - TOT Taarab Vol - 25: [Compilation], 2000; AD_MC_035_ref1125; 1 Cassettes
  - TOT Taarab Vol - 32: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1126; 1 Cassettes
  - Tushauriane Kimenishinda: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1127; 1 Cassettes
  - Ubin-Adam Kazi: Juma Nature, AD_MC_035_ref1128; 1 Cassettes
  - Vibuzi Upele: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1129; 1 Cassettes
  - Vol. 22 Mwanamke Mazingira: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1130; 1 Cassettes
  - Vugo La Rasini: [Unknown], AD_MC_035_ref1131; 1 Cassettes
  - Wagosi Wa Kaya: Ukweli Mtupu, AD_MC_035_ref1132; 1 Cassettes
  - Wana Metro 'B': [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1133; 1 Cassettes
  - Wanyama Wakali: Jamhuri Jazz Band, AD_MC_035_ref1134; 1 Cassettes
  - Wapendanao: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1135; 1 Cassettes
  - Yusuf Mohamed (Tenge): Yusuf Mohamed (Tenge), AD_MC_035_ref1136; 1 Cassettes
  - Hawaumi Hawarambi: Yusuf Mohamed (Tenge), AD_MC_035_ref1137; 1 Cassettes
  - Zaire Bin Ya Mama 4: [Unknown], AD_MC_035_ref1138; 1 Cassettes
  - Zaire Khonjokolio: [Unknown], AD_MC_035_ref1139; 1 Cassettes
  - Zanzibar Favorites Vol. 1: Saif Salim with Leo Band, AD_MC_035_ref1140; 1 Cassettes
  - Zanzibar Nuimbo Za Taarab: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1141; 1 Cassettes
  - Zanzibar Stars Modern Taarab. Unalo Lilokukaa Na Roho: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1142; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein 8: Zein, AD_MC_035_ref1143; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein Concerts 9: Zein Musical Party, AD_MC_035_ref1144; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein Concert No. 19: Zein, AD_MC_035_ref1145; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein's concerts no. 20: Zein Musical Party, AD_MC_035_ref1146; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein concerts 20: Zein Musical Party, AD_MC_035_ref1147; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein concert 25: Zein Musical Party, AD_MC_035_ref1148; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein Concerts 33: Zein, AD_MC_035_ref1149; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein Concerts 34: Zein Musical Party, AD_MC_035_ref1150; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein at Germany 1999: Zein, AD_MC_035_ref1151; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein Selected Songs #1: Zein Musical Party, AD_MC_035_ref1152; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein Vol. No. 5: Zein Musical Party, AD_MC_035_ref1153; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein Vol. No. 8: Zein Musical Party, AD_MC_035_ref1154; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein Vol. No. 10: Zein Musical Party, AD_MC_035_ref1155; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein Vol. No. 11: Zein Musical Party, AD_MC_035_ref1156; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein Vol. No. 12: Zein Musical Party, AD_MC_035_ref1157; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein Vol. No. 13: Zein Musical Party, AD_MC_035_ref1158; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein Vol. No. 14: Zein Musical Party, AD_MC_035_ref1159; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein Vol. 15: Zein Musical Party, AD_MC_035_ref1160; 1 Cassettes
  - Zenji Flava: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1162; 1 Cassettes
  - Zilizopendwa 1980's Utapenda: John Nzenze Amutabi, AD_MC_035_ref1163; 1 Cassettes
  - Zilizopendwa 1992 Edition: Uyoga, AD_MC_035_ref1164; 1 Cassettes
  - Zilizovuma: [Compilation], 2005; AD_MC_035_ref1165; 1 Cassettes
  - Zuhura 1: [Unknown], AD_MC_035_ref1166; 1 Cassettes
  - Zuhura Swaleh: Maulidi Musical Party, AD_MC_035_ref1167; 1 Cassettes
  - Old Bhalo No. 3: Bhalo & Party, AD_MC_035_ref1168; 1 Cassettes
  - Maulidi Juma 22B: Maulidi Juma, AD_MC_035_ref1169; 1 Cassettes
  - Maulidi Juma 21B: Maulidi Juma, AD_MC_035_ref1170; 1 Cassettes
  - Maulidi Juma 24B: Maulidi Juma, AD_MC_035_ref1171; 1 Cassettes
  - Best of Rusha Roho: [Compilation], AD_MC_035_ref1172; 1 Cassettes
  - Shakila: Shakila, AD_MC_035_ref1173; 1 Cassettes
  - Zein Vol. 16: Zein Musical Party, AD_MC_035_ref1161; 1 Cassettes